

Vinh Pham

IT Manager at United International Pharma

Connect

♠ Message

More...



Try Premium Free for 1 Month



Connect

△ Message

• • •

Vinh Pham · 3rd

IT Manager at United International Pharma

Vietnam · 500+ connections · Contact info

United International Pharma

Economics University of Ho Chi Minh City

People and pages related to Vinh

See all

×

>



Pfizer

Page • Pharmaceuticals 4,059,566 followers

Follow



Pharma Jobs (Pharma Wisdom Jobs)

Page • Pharmaceuticals 186,013 followers

Follow



AbbVie

Page • Pharmaceuticals 709,718 followers

Follow

About

Experienced Information Technology Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the pharmaceuticals industry. Skilled in Business Process, Enterprise Software, ITIL, Customer Relationship Management (CRM), and Sales Management. Strong information technology professional with a BA focused in Business Administration fro

... see more

Activity

629 followers

Posts Vinh created, shared, or commented on in the last 90 days are displayed here.

See all activity

Experience

IT Manager

United International Pharma Apr 2011 – Present · 10 yrs 1 mo

Customer Support Manager

Exact
Oct 2000 – Mar 2011
· 10 yrs 6 mos
Vietnam

Deputy Director of FIBI Hanoi

FIBI

Sep 1994 – Sep 2000

· 6 yrs 1 mo

Education

Economics University of Ho Chi Minh City

BA, Business Administration 1988 – 1992

Skills & endorsements

IT Management . 7

=Exact

Endorsed by 3 of Vinh's colleagues at Exact

ERP . 12

Duc Thao Nguyen and 11 connections have given endorsements for this skill

ITIL . 5

Duc Thao Nguyen and 4 connections have given endorsements for this skill

Industry Knowledge

 $\textbf{Project Management}_{~\cdot~4}$

Business Process . 2
CRM . ₁
Business Intelligence . 4
Software Project Management . 4
Integration . 3
Vendor Management . 2
Consultancy
Sales Management
Management Consulting
Information Technology
Business Management
Tools & Technologies
Enterprise Software . 1
Interpersonal Skills
Leadership
Customer Service
Management
Other Skills Other Skills
Exact

Interests

Prudential Vietnam Assurance Private Ltd.



22,796 followers

Looking for an IT Manager/Project Manager position

259 followers

Suntory PepsiCo Vietnam Beverage

39,253 followers



Exact

74,547 followers

=exact

Deloitte Consulting



195,016 followers

Hongkong Land Limited

39,898 followers



People also viewed



Phung Le •3rd

C&B Assistant Manager at United International Pharma Co.,Ltd

Connect



Lê Thảo •3rd

Financial Planning and Analysis Asistant Manager at United International Pharma Co., Ltd

Connect



Phuong Nguyen •2nd

Operational IT Assistant Manager at United International Pharma

Connect



Khanh Nguyen •3rd

Head of Trade Marketing Pharmaceutical & Aesthetic

Connect



UNITED INTERNATIONAL PHARMA •3rd

Talent Acquisition Team - Career Website: unitedpharmacareer.com

Connect

People you may know



BE BA (My Nguyen)

Recruitment Specialist cum Admin at Milensea Retail

Connect



Le Nhat Huy

President at UTE Logistics and Supply Chain Club

Connect



Khánh Linh Đỗ

Human Resources Assistant at Hachinet Software

Connect



Nguyen Dinh Dat

Frontend Angular Developer

Connect



Nhi Duong

Student at Ton Duc Thang University

Connect

∨Show more

Duc, learn what hiring managers look for in answers to top interview questions



Careers

Marketing Solutions

Privacy & Terms 🗸



